Nathan Atherton

Currently living in North West UK Tel: 07584032425

https://nathanatherton.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathan-atherton/ Email: nathanatherton2@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am currently a Intermediate Frontend Web Developer working to tight deadlines creating stunning websites for high calibre clients. I have also recently completed a bachelor degree, studying in Web Design and Development, achieving a first class grade. Prior to this, a 15-month long apprenticeship in Marketing and Graphic and Design Media was completed. I have had a lot of experience in technology and keeping up to date with the latest new releases that are related to computers specifically. I have previously built a PC with the specs of 8GB Memory, a GTX 980Ti GPU, and an intel i5-3750k CPU. I have previously been consistent with editing videos and creating thumbnails and logos, these were then implemented on YouTube. I have also been involved in game testing, testing a game named 'Iron fish' which was released as a full PC Indie game.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

September 2016 – July 2019 1st Class Bachelors with Honours Web Design and Development Edge Hill University

June 2016 – July 2016 Grade – Pass Edge Hill Fastrack Edge Hill University

November 2014 - February 2016 Edexcel Level 3 Diploma in Create and Digital Media (QCF) Versa Ltd November 2014 – February 2016 Edexcel BTEC Level 3 Certificate in Creative and Digital Media (QCF) Versa Ltd

September 2013 – October 2014 2 AS LevelsDeanery Sixth Form
Wigan

September 2008 – July 2013 10 GCSE's above grade C Deanery C of E High School Wigan

SKILLS

- Adobe Premiere Pro Video Editing
- Adobe Photoshop Photo Editing
- Adobe Illustrator Vector Drawings
- Sony Vegas Video Editing
- Adobe After Effects Video Editing
- HTML
- CSS
- LESS

- JavaScript
- JQuery
- ReactJS
- React Native
- JSP
- JSON
- XML
- Advanced Microsoft Word

CAREER SUMMARY

July 2019 - Present

Cheshire Datasystems Limited (CDL)

Intermediate Front End Web Developer

- Developing products whilst working in an Agile development lifecycle
- Assisting in sizing requirements for a product
- Translating UX / UI designs to dynamic websites
- Working within a squad to produce web sites
- Writing clean, efficient code to create the best product that meets the customer requirements

May 2016 - June 2019

McDonald's

Crew Member

- Leading a kitchen of at least 5 people, ensuring that all food is cooked to the highest of quality.
- Cooking food in a fast manner to meet customer expectations
- Spoken to customers and correctly taken their orders
- Handled cash from customers when orders have been taken

November 2014 - February 2016

Versa Ltd

Marketing Apprentice

- Created designs for advertisements
- Created line drawings of products, such as benches and bike shelters
- File Management
- Managing the company Social Media accounts
- Writing Blog Posts

July 2012 - July 2012

Heinz

Work Experience

- Organised Spreadsheets
- Used purchasing system
- Created engineering jobs on internal system

INTERESTS

I am interested in keeping up to date with football, I enjoy attending football matches in my spare time, I support Wigan Athletic and have followed this team throughout all my life. Another of my interests that I do partake in during my free time is that I follow esports, the main game that is involved in the esports that I follow is called Rocket League, I have also partaken in some tournaments in this game, which has always kept my interest as high as possible in the esports scene.

REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE ON REQUEST